孩子们  我已经讲过了所有 重大节日的故事了
Kids, I told you stories about all the big holidays--
圣诞节
Christmas...
万圣节
Halloween...
感恩节
Thanksgiving...
但有一个节日永远是我的最爱
but one holiday was always my favorite--
超级碗杯 (美国橄榄球大联盟的决赛)
Super Bowl Sunday.
2007年的超级碗
And there was one Super Bowl back in 2007
我永远都忘不了
that I will never forget.
马修  你负责啤酒
Marshall, you're on beer detail.
莉莉  你来做土豆泥
Lily, you're making the bean dip.
罗宾  你负责薯片和椒盐卷饼
Uh, Robin, you're on chips and pretzels,
巴尼  我不派你做事了
and Barney, I'm giving you nothing to do
你只要注意你的赌博问题就好
so you can just focus on controlling your gambling problem.
"问题"?
"Problem."
可怜的超人
Oh, poor Superman, he should really do something
他真的应该注意 一下他的飞行问题
about his flying problem.
如果你很在行 那就不算是个问题
It's not a problem if you're awesome at it.
而我要去奎恩那儿 带些超棒的食物
And I will be going to Quinn's to pick up the world's greatest food,
超级碗杯辣鸡翅拼盘
the Super Bowl Hot Wings Platter.
如果我是那只鸡 我愿意去食人族那儿看那些坏小子
If I were a chicken, I'd go cannibal for those bad boys.
吃了我那该死的翅膀吧 我不在乎...
Just eat my own damn wing off. I don't care.
我超爱看的
I'm crazy like that.
这是明晚的活动安排
Here's the info for tomorrow night.
明晚什么事?
What's tomorrow night?
上帝  你们还不知道?
Oh, God, you didn't hear?
马克死了
Mark died.
- 天哪 - 上帝啊
- Oh, my God. - Oh, my gosh.
明晚6点举行葬礼
The funeral's tomorrow at 6:00, and I know
如果你们能来 马克的在天之灵也会感激的
it would have meant a lot to Mark if you came.
你们是他最喜欢的顾客了
You guys were his favorite customers.
- 坚强点 - 我们很遗憾
- Stay strong. - We're so sorry.
谁是马克?
Who was Mark?
- 不知道 - 不清楚
- No idea. - Not a clue.
那我们应该要去?
Well, I guess we should go, right?
等等...明天晚上6点 那是超级碗杯的时间
Wait... tomorrow night at 6:00, that's the Super Bowl.
我感到很遗憾 但我们真的不认识麦克
Okay, I feel terrible, but the truth is we didn't know Mike.
- 马克 - 马克
- Mark. - Mark,
所以只要我们送了花
and as long as we send flowers,
我想不出我们 一定要去的理由了
I can't think of any reason we'd have to go.
滚出去!
Get out of here!
我不想在这里再看到你了
I never want to see your face in this bar again!
那个没心没肺的混蛋刚刚告诉我说 因为他想看超级杯
This soulless bastard just told me he can't come to Mark's funeral
所以他不能去马克的葬礼了
because he wants to watch the Super Bowl.
你们能相信?
Could you believe that?
你们会来吧?
You guys are coming, right?
对...绝不会错过的
Yes... Wouldn't miss for the world.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第二季 第十四集
翻译：    melodyzheng        校对：     雨亦奇
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
只能这么着了...
Okay, here's the plan :
录下比赛 去葬礼...
record the game, go to the funeral,
- 向麦特致敬 - 马克!
- pay our respects to Matt... - Mark.
马克... 然后在1小时后继续看比赛
Mark, and start watching only an hour late.
要保证能录到
Okay, that's great, but just to make sure it records,
也许我们应该低头  向TiVo神 (TiVo:数位硬碟式录影机)
maybe we should bow our heads and say a quiet prayer
祈祷一下
to the TiVo gods.
万能的TiVo
Almighty TiVo,
我们感谢所有 你给予我们的礼物
we thank you for all the gifts you have given us:
能暂停直播电视 让我们方便一下的能力
the power to freeze live TV to go take a leak
这种能力伟大如神
is nothing short of Godlike.
当然还有在广告时间快进的力量
Let's not forget fast-forwarding through commercials.
向你再提出任何要求有点贪心了
It seems greedy to ask anything more from you,
神奇的盒子
O magic box,
但如果你出现故障 漏录了超级碗杯的话
but if you malfunction and miss the Super Bowl,
我们会用棒球棒 在巷子里蹂躏你
we will destroy you in the alley with baseball bats.
- 阿门 - 阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
广告时候 我们没有快进啊
We are not fast-forwarding through the commercials.
对  那是最好看的部分
Yeah, they're the best part.
算了吧  还记得去年吗?
Oh, come on. Remember last year?
是谁想看穿着椰子胸罩 猴子点披萨的?
Who wants to watch a monkey in a coconut bra order a pizza?
那只猴子真可爱
Oh, my God. This monkey was so cute.
这是我今天最后一次打给你了
Seriously, that's the last time I'm gonna call you today.
好的
Okay.
再见
G ood-bye.
你也没挂
You didn't hang up either!
我知道  你先挂
I know! You hang up!
你先挂
You hang up!
我的庄家  人挺好
My bookie. Great guy.
我直说了吧 你去葬礼难道不该穿西装?
So let me get this straight. A funeral is the one time you don't suit up?
我没教过你吗  泰德
Have I taught you nothing, Ted?
的确没有
Virtually.
西装在裁缝界是快乐的象征
Suits are full of joy.
这种快乐单纯如婴儿的笑脸
They're the sartorial equivalent of a baby's smile.
"裁缝界"?
"Sartorial"?
相关裁缝或那个行业的
"Of or pertaining to tailors or their trade."
西装是给活着的人的
Suits are for the living.
所以到我与世长辞的时候
That's why when it's my time to R.I.P.
我要像刚到这个世界时一样的
I'm going out of this world the same way I came into it--
赤裸裸
buck naked. Yeah.
那会很棒的
It's gonna be awesome.
男人们就在酒吧里寻欢 为女士们打开棺材让她们瞻仰
Open bar for the guys, open casket for the ladies.
怎么样?
What up?!
- 真可惜 - 是啊
- Such a waste. - I know.
他还这么年轻
He was so young.
手织羊绒双排扣的D&G西装
A hand-stitched, cashmere, double-breasted Dolce & Gabbana.
他肯定很害怕
It must be so frightened.
进度比我想像得快
This is going faster than I thought.
我们去酒吧 意思一下守灵
We'll make an appearance at the bar for the wake,
我们8点就能开始看比赛了
we'll be watching the game by 8:00.
即使那天我们没看到一条鲸鱼
And even though we didn't see any whales,
马克和我仍然认为那是我们 生命中最美好的一天
Mark and I both said it was the best day of our lives.
我要再去转一圈了
Okay, I'm getting us another round.
等我回来
And when I come back,
每个人都说个 你最爱的关于马克的故事
everyone else is telling their favorite Mark story.
卡尔刚才讲的故事我要了
Dibs on the one Carl just told.
再过个超级碗杯的时间 我就要去上班了
Okay, I have to be at work exactly one Super Bowl from now.
面对现实吧 我们不可能去看了
Oh, let's face it, we're not going to get to watch it.
我们只要知道分数就行了
We  should just find out the score.
谢天谢地  我来问
Oh, thank God! I'll find out.
不...不...不行! 我们要一起看比赛
No, no, no, we can't! We have to watch the game together.
这是传统...
It's tradition.
想想我们一起看比赛的 那些快乐的时光
Think of all the great times we've had watching this game.
2次触地  大家喝啊
Second down, everyone drink.
这不是个喝酒比赛
Ted, it's not a drinking game
你喝酒的时候 什么事都会发生
if you drink anytime anything happens.
这些是鸡翅还是天使的翅膀
Are these chicken wings or angel wings?
我太爱吃了
God, I love these things.
我爱你们
I love you guys.
这真是太棒了 我们一起看超级碗
This is so great, all of us watching the Super Bowl together.
这很特别
This is special.
我们每年都要这么做 答应我
We need to do this every year-- promise me!
冷静点  兄弟
Calm down, buddy.
放广告了
Oh, commercials!
大家干杯!
Everyone drink!
这真是个好传统 我们大家一起看比赛
God, this is such a great tradition, all of us watching the game together.
这是怎么开始的?
How did this start?
巴尼  我赌20块 凯西进不了球
Hey, Barney, I bet you 20 bucks that Casey misses this field goal.
我不赌 只有傻子才打赌
I don't bet. Betting's for suckers.
赌个1美元啊什么的 这没什么大不了
Make it like a dollar or something, you know. Who cares? No big deal.
好吧
Fine.
看吧  给你 他进球了  你赢了
See, there you go, he made it. You win.
等等  这是我的? 就这样?
Wait. This is mine, just like that?
天那  这感觉太好了
God, that feels good.
不  这感觉真是... 太好了
No, that feels really... good.
还有什么能赌的?
What else can we bet on?
没了  现在中场表演了
Nothing, it's the halftime show.
太糟了
Oh, so lame.
都没人注意吗?
Nobody even pays attention.
看呢  珍妮・杰克逊!谁在乎啊? (在中场表演中露乳)
I mean, Janet Jackson, who cares?
天啊  罗宾多棒啊!
God, how cool is Robin?
真不敢相信你在 我们这个神圣的日子里
I can't believe you invited this girl we've only known for a few months
邀请一个只认识了 几个月而已的女孩来
to  our sacred day.
现在所有的照片里都会有她了
Now she's gonna be in all the pictures.
是啊  是啊  无所谓 我赌  海鹰队
Yeah, yeah, whatever. I'll give you the Seahawks
赢6分  赌500美金
plus six points for 500 bucks.
你疯拉  50还差不多
Are you crazy? Maybe for $50.
50美金?50美金有什么意思?
$50?! What fun is $50?!
我们干脆赌空气算了 天啊  马修
Why don't we just bet air?! God, Marshall!
好吧  就50美金
Okay, $50.
算我一份
Hey, I'll take that action.
海鹰队  赢4分 但是赌1000块
Seahawks, but make it four points and make it a grand.
这些鸡翅   到底是鸡翅 还是天使的翅膀
Hey, these wings, are they chicken wings or angel wings?
广告!
Oh, commercials!
穿着椰子胸罩的猴子  太好笑了
Monkey with a coconut bra. Hilarious.
看吧  我们一直一起看超级杯的
Look, we always watch the Super Bowl together.
那么我们约好了 明天6点再看
So we make a pact to watch it tomorrow at 6:00
接下来的18个小时里 不准打听谁赢了比赛
and go the next 18 hours without finding out who won.
那怎么可能
That's impossible.
我不想骗你  那确实很难
I'm not gonna lie to you. It's not gonna be easy.
那意味着不准看电视  不准上网
That means no TV, no Internet,
不看报纸  什么都不做
no newspapers, nothing.
断绝一切媒体
Media blackout.
但我们的传统能继续
But our tradition lives on.
谁要参加?
Who's in?
- 我 - 我
- I'm in. - I'm in.
- 我 - 该死的  我也参加
- I'm in. - What the hell, I'm in.
- 击掌 - 兄弟 我们可是在守灵
- High five! - Dude, we're at a wake.
对不起  那严肃的击一下吧
Sorry. Solemn low five.
当第二天来临 我们中没有人知道
As the day began, none of us had any idea how hard it would be
要在9小时内不听到任何 关于超级碗的消息有多难
to go nine hours without hearing the outcome of the Super Bowl.
我决定在家工作
I decided to work from home to avoid contamination
以免被外面的世界污染到
by the outside world.
拿着这钥匙  吞下去
Hey, take this key and swallow it.
什么?不
What? No.
快点  泰德  然后沙拉 到比赛的时候就能拉出来了
Come on, Ted, you eat salads. It'll be out by game time.
那更不行了
Lots more, no.
我可不是在胡闹  西奥多
I'm not messing around, Theodore.
我在这场比赛上赌了很多钱
I've got a lot of money riding on this game.
如果我不把我自己 烤在这个散热片上的话
If I don't handcuff myself to this radiator,
我就会去查比分了 快拿好钥匙
I'll check the score. Please take the key.
好吧
Fine.
但我同意是因为你没考虑 怎么上厕所的问题
But only because you didn't think through a bathroom plan
而且我觉得那样会很有趣的
and I think that's funny.
断绝媒体对罗宾来说特别难
The media blackout was particularly hard on Robin
因为   她就是媒体
because, well, she was the media.
但是不幸的是  市政府无法
But unfortunately, the City won't be fixing
马上修补这个大路坑
the unusually large pothole any time soon,
所以如果你在布鲁克林至皇后区 高速公路行驶  请系紧安全带
so buckle up if you're on the BQE.
那里会很颠簸的
It's gonna be a bumpy one.
看起来上班族还有更多的罪要受
Like morning commutes needed to get any harder.
没错  凯文
You're right, Kevin.
好的  罗宾  你看是不是到时候 让西德来报道
Well, Robin, what do you say? I think it's time to check in with Sid
- 最新的体育消息了 - 不!
- for a sports update. - No!
- 什么? - 不
- What? - No.
现在是体育新闻时间了
But it's, uh, time for Sports.
不...不是... 现在是天气预报时间
No, it's not. It's time for Weather.
我们刚才报过了
We, we just did Weather.
气象非常多变
Well, weather's pretty fickle,
也许现在已经变了
it may have changed.
你那里现在怎么样了  罗?
What's it doing out there, Lou?
基本和2分钟前没什么差别
Pretty much the same thing it was two minutes ago.
回你那里了  罗宾
Back to you, Robin.
好的  现在是体育新闻时间
Okay, now it's time for Sports.
不!我们来看看交通情况
No! Let's go to Traffic Todd
来自地铁的新闻 一架用于堵塞时的直升机
in the Metro News 1 Gridlock Chopper.
罗宾  现在是体育新闻时间!
Robin, it's time for Sports!
到你了   西德
Over to you, Sid.
谢谢  凯文和罗宾
Thank you, Kevin and Robin.
让我们来看看超级碗杯吧
Let's talk about the Super Bowl.
几星期前 马修答应莉莉
Weeks earlier, Marshall had promised Lily
他会去她幼儿园班级的开放日
he'd come into her kindergarten class for show-and-tell day.
而且他有双重关节...
And he's a little bit double-jointed...
他最喜欢的动物是尼斯湖水怪
And his favorite animal is the Loch Ness monster.
莉莉  我说多少次了
Lily, how many times...?
尼斯是一种很友好的生物
Nessie is a gentle creature.
我们尽量不称它为"怪物"
We're trying to stay away from terms like "Monster."
我想我们都同意 他比莎莉的独眼金鱼
Well, I think we can all agree, he is much more interesting
有趣多了
than Sally's one-eyed goldfish.
连续3个礼拜? 别这样了  莎莉
Three weeks in a row? Come on, Sally.
好了  那么剩下的时间
Okay, well, that's all the time we have.
大家开始画画和做手工吧
Arts and crafts, everybody.
我是多齐
Hey. I'm Doug.
我是马修
Oh, hey, I'm Marshall.
你今天一天都要呆在这里?
Are you going to be staying here for the rest of day?
是的 其实我是躲在这儿
Yeah, I'm actually trying to hide out
因为我不想知道谁赢了超级杯
'cause I don't want to know who won the Super Bowl.
我知道谁赢了
I know who won.
那很好 但我真的不想知道
Oh, um, that's great, but I really don't want to know,
所以可以的话 你自己知道就行了
so if you could just keep that to yourself.
你有多不想知道啊?
How badly do you not want to know?
什么意思?
Excuse me?
10块
Ten bucks.
你是认真的?
Are you serious?
现在升到8块了 (分不清数字大小的孩子)
Just went up to eight.
放开我  泰德
Unlock me, Ted.
我从来没有这么长 时间不打给庄家过
I've never gone this long without calling my bookie.
他会担心的
He worries.
看完比赛就放你
Not until game time.
你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
去取我的鸡翅
Pick up the hot wings.
什么?你脑子进水了?
What? How the hell are you planning on getting
去体育酒吧怎么可能不知道比分?
in and out of a sports bar without seeing the score?
那里到处都是电视
There's TVs everywhere.
别担心
Ah, don't worry.
我都计划好了
I got it all planned out.
首先
First of all:
我在太阳镜上贴上胶带
I placed duct tape on a pair of sunglasses
我只能从两个小洞里往外看
so I can only see out of two tiny holes.
然后  我用旧麦片盒做了马眼罩
Next, I constructed blinders out of an old cereal box.
还有  高科技除噪耳机
Top it all off: high-tech noise-reducing headphones
马修和莉莉第一次回来时我买的
I bought when Marshall and Lily first got back together
它作用很大
and were doing it a lot.
我称它为感官剥夺器5000
I call it the Sensory Deprivator 5000.
你好  我叫泰德・莫斯比
Hello! Uh, my name is Ted Mosby.
我来这儿取我的辣鸡翅
I'm here to pick up my hot wings.
在我手里 你会找到鸡翅的钱
In my hand, you'll find the exact total for the wings
还有非常慷慨的小费
plus a generous tip.
请拿走钱
Please take the cash.
把鸡翅放我手里 然后我就回去了
Put the wings in my hand and I'll be on my way.
谢谢你
Thank you!
就这样本次超级碗杯终于结束了
And that closes the book on one heck of a Super Bowl.
还给你们了  凯文  罗宾
Back  to you, Kevin and Robin.
我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
而且是清醒得回来
And we're clear.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
罗宾  是我弄错了
Um, Robin, is it just me,
还是你想与众不同?
or were you doing something different there?
我还没看比赛
I haven't watched the game yet.
我求你了 剩下的新闻里
I'm begging you, for the rest of the newscast
不要出现任何谁赢了超级杯的资料
there can't be any references to who won the Super Bowl.
我是说  把提词机里也改了
I mean, change the teleprompter.
不要有队伍的名字  没有特征
No team names, nothing specific.
这太疯狂了  我不能那么做
That is crazy. I can't do that.
我的朋友马克这个星期去世了
My friend Mark passed away this week.
好了  亲爱的  好了 好的  我很遗憾
Okay, sweety okay. Okay, I'm so sorry.
Back in five... four...
这太难过了
- three... - It's just so hard.
8分23秒之后...
现在谁才是傻瓜！
Ha! Who's the idiot now?!
你说感官剥夺器5000很蠢吗
You said the Sensory Deprivator 5000 was stupid.
但它完全奏效了
But it totally worked!
我周围发生的事 我都看不见也听不见
I couldn't see or hear anything happening around me.
看吧  看吧
Right?! Right?!
不!
No...!
如果那还不够糟的话
And if that weren't bad enough,
我马上就要有个更痛苦的发现了
I was about to have a horrible realization.
豉油酱呢?
Where's the dipping sauce?
赢了的那队 你想知道和他名字押韵的词吗?
The team that won, want to know what their name rhymes with?
别这样  伙计 你说过我把蜡笔都吃了
Come on, dude. You promised you'd stop
你就不再为难我了
if I ate all those crayons.
你干嘛这么做?
Why are you doing this?
我爱上艾得仁小姐了
I'm in love with Miss Aldrin.
你不可能得到艾得仁小姐 她是我的...
Well, you can't have Miss Aldrin, she's mine.
好了  这是谁干的?
Okay, now who did this?
我干的
I did.
是不是马修要去罚站了?
Does that mean Marshall gets a time-out?
马修是大人  所以...
Well, Marshall's a grownup, so...
我们打破东西的时候 都要罚站的
When one of us breaks something, we get a time-out.
对不起了
S orry.
超级碗杯结束后
And after the Super Bowl,
输的那队的城市的市长要进贡
the mayor of the losing team's city had to pay up,
送15磅他或她城里最著名的食物
sending the mayor of the winning team's city
给赢了的那队所在的城市
15 pounds of a delicacy his or her city is famous for.
现在最好把烤肉架 蒸笼或油锅准备好
Better fire up whatever type of grill, steamer or fryer
你可能要用到它们来煮贡品
one might use to cook that delicacy, Winning Team's Mayor.
Hey.
我不想和你说话
- Hey. - I'm not talking to you.
不 你想...
Yes, you are.
你要按我说的做
You'll do whatever I say.
- 屏住呼吸 - 我不会屏住呼吸的
- Hold your breath. - I'm not holding my breath.
获胜的队伍是...
The winning team was the...
那么我们就这么解决吧
Now here's how this is going to work:
你每星期给我带3部成人级的电影
you're going to take me to three R-rated movies a week...
然后马修叔叔有了个主意
And then Uncle Marshall got an idea.
他回顾这主意不是那么得意
It was not one he was proud of in retrospect,
但在如此绝望的时候...
but desperate times...
不
Oh, no.
有人尿湿裤子了
Somebody wet their pants.
- 不  不是我干的 - 真的吗?
- No, I didn't. - Oh, really?
大家会相信谁呢?
Who's everyone gonna believe?
我是一个成年的哥伦比亚大学 法律系3年级的大人
I'm a grownup third-year law student at Columbia
而你只是小小尿裤子先生 现在我问你个问题
and you're just a little pants wetter. So now I ask you a question:
你想悄悄地 溜到洗手间弄干裤子
You want to be able to quietly sneak off to the restroom and dry off
还是让我把它 当成今天的活动主题?
or am I gonna have something for show and tell today?
- 所有人... - 好吧 好吧
- Hey, everyone... - Okay, okay.
你赢了
You win.
把钱还给我
I want my money back.
还有你的布丁点心
And your pudding snack pack.
先生  谁赢了超级碗杯?
Sir, who won the Super Bowl?
对不起  我没看比赛
Sorry. I missed the game.
你没看?  他怎么能没看?
You missed...?! How could he miss...?
不好意思!  谁赢了碗超级杯?!
Excuse me! Who won the Super Bowl?!
我...不太看体育
I... don't really follow sports.
天啊!
Oh, my...!
艾米特・史密斯 (美国橄榄球明星)
Emmitt Smith!
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
是的  很多人谢过我了
Yeah, I get that a lot.
你一定要告诉我 谁赢了超级碗杯?
You got to tell me, who won the Super Bowl?
昨晚的比赛？
The game was last night?
要是你赢了2或3次那种比赛
You know, once you win two or three of those things,
它就有点像是...
it's kind of like, eh.
但你是艾米特・史密斯  你是橄榄球员啊 那可是超级碗杯日啊
But you're Emmitt Smith. You're a football player, it's Super Bowl Sunday.
有什么会比橄榄球更重要?!
What could possibly be more important than football?!
跳舞  我的朋友  跳舞 (他参加了美国真人秀：与明星共舞)
Dance, my friend. Dance.
不!
N o...!
你好  又是我
Hello! It's me again.
我怎么会不认识你...
Oh! I didn't recognize you.
你忘了给我豉油酱了!
Yeah, you forgot to give me the dipping sauce!
噢  对
Ah. Yes.
就是这个
This is the one.
现在是4点  目前来看 我们都完成了不可能的任务
It was 4:00, and so far, all of us had done the impossible.
但是接下来  几乎是同时
But then, almost simultaneously,
事情开始变糟了
things started to go wrong.
让我们用快乐的音符来结束这一天
And let's end the day on a happy note.
布朗克斯动物园有最新消息
There is a new arrival at the Bronx Zoo.
泰里斯・桑切斯带来的报道
Trish Sanchez has the story.
- 伙计 - 伙计  当心
- Hey, buddy. - Hey, dude, look out.
由于昨晚在赢得超级碗杯之后
And in honor of yesterday's big win...
- 伙计  当心 - 伙计  小心啊!
- Hey, buddy, look out. - Dude, watch out!
公园决定命名公园决定
...the zoo decided to name the baby panda
用胜队为小熊猫命名为...
after Super Bowl champions...
不!
No...!
太好了!
Yes...!
太棒了  正是开赛的时候
Awesome. Just in time for kick-off.
你们都不知道比分  对吧?
None of you guys found out the score, right?
- 完成任务 - 不知道
- Mission accomplished. - Didn't find out.
太好了  我们开始吧 我已经快进好了
Great. Let's do it. I already fast-forwarded
闯过了比赛前4小时的新闻轰炸
through the four hours of pre-game coverage. So we are ready.
巴尼  我都不能看你了
Barney, I can't even look at you.
我不想看到任何关于 谁赢了比赛的信号
I don't want any sign of who won.
别担心  我不会给你 任何消息的
Don't worry, I'm not going to give anything away.
不要管我  开始吧
Feel free to start without me.
愚蠢!愚蠢!愚蠢!
Ah...! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
那么多钱!你搞砸了  巴尼!
So much money! You screwed it up, Barney!
你把一切都搞砸了! 愚蠢!愚蠢!愚蠢!
You screwed everything up! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
好了  我们看比赛吧
Okay, let's watch the game.
巴尼  你该死的在干什么了? 我们知道你赌谁赢了
Barney, what the hell was that? We know who you bet on.
现在你把所有人的比赛都毁了
Now you've ruined the game for everyone.
是的 谢谢了 巴尼
Yeah. Thanks a lot, Barney.
都被毁了
Way to blow it.
是啊  我不知道的 现在我知道了
Yeah, I didn't know and now I do know.
现在根本没必要看比赛了
There's no point in even watching the game.
至少广告没被毁了
Well, at least the commercials aren't ruined.
鸡翅还是不错的
Wings are still good.
啤酒还能喝啊
Beer still works.
该死的
Ah, what the hell.
我们来看看巴尼怎么输的钱
Let's watch Barney lose some money.
听着
Hey, so check this out:
我今天被一个5岁的人敲诈了
I got extorted by a five-year-old today.
我今天差点被炒了
I almost got fired today.
我今天遇到艾米特・史密斯了
I met Emmitt Smith today.
你先说
Ooh, you go first.
我实验了 我的感官剥夺器5000
I tried out the Sensory Deprivator 5000.
对  继续  巴尼
Yeah, go ahead, Barney.
我疯了似的冲下街
Well, I was frantically running down the street
想要知道比赛的结果
trying to find out the score to the game...
接下来就有趣了
And here's the funny part,
像那么难忘的一次超级杯
as unforgettable as that Super Bowl was,
23年之后  我不记得谁赢了
here it is 23 years later and I don't remember who won...
我甚至不记得谁参赛了
Hell, I don't even remember who played.
我记得的是  我们喝了啤酒
What I do remember is that we drank beer,
我们吃了鸡翅  然后 我们一起看了超级杯
we ate wings and we watched the Super Bowl together.
因为有时  即使你知道 有些事的结局
Because sometimes, even if you know how something's going to end,
那并不意味着 你不能享受它的过程
that doesn't mean you can't enjoy the ride.
我们甚至还敬了老朋友马克一杯
We even raised a toast to good old Mike.
他叫马克?马特?
I mean Mark. Matt.
废话!  我为什么老是这样?
Crap! Why do I keep doing that?
我不只输了比赛 我输了所有的投注
I didn't only lose the game, I lost every single prop bet.
罚码总数  重战次数
Total penalty yardage, number of replay-challenges,
扔硬币的结果
coin toss...
输了扔硬币结果的比率是多少?
What are the odds of losing the coin toss?
5对5  输或赢都一样
50-50, give or take.
拦截  触地得分  抢球总数
Interceptions, field-goals, total sacks,
不管怎么样  总有样安全的 首先...
whether or not there'd be a safety, first...